Guide to the Stanford University, Haas Center for Public Service, Records SC0541
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2009-042
  - Student Organization Descriptions, Subseries 2
    - SAC [Stanford Advocates for Children], 2001-02 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - SAHC [Stanford Affordable Housing Coalition], 2001-02 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Stanford Community Carnival, 2001-02 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Stanford Health Corps, 1995-96, 2001-02 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Stanford Youth Forensics, 2001-02 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Student Organizing Committee for the Arts, 2001-02 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - SYP [Stanford Youth Project], 2001-02 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - TABS [Technology Assist By Students], Undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Stanford TAIKO, 2001-02 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - TEAM [Together Each Accomplishes More], 2001-02 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - United Students for Veteran Health, Undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Upward Bound, 1993, 1999-02 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - VIA, 2002-04 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - WICS [Women in Computer Science], Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - WYSE [Women and Youth Supporting Each Other], 1999-02 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Student Activism (includes photographs), 2002 and undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Files from Olivia Torbett (Associate Director of Administrative Services), Subseries 3
    - Service-learning, Courses, and Curriculum
      - Children and Society, 1992-94 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Prep for Internship Learning, 1993-96 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Urban Studies, 1993, 1996-97 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Motivated to Serve, 1989, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Assorted Courses, 1988, 1992-94 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Process and Practice of Community Service, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Philanthropy Seminar, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Community Service Writing Program, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Study-Service Connections, 1987-97 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Public Service Scholars, 1994-98 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Service-Learning Working Group, 1996-98 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Public Service Jobs and Internships
      - Job Support Group, Jan, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Palo Alto Fund, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Summer Job Workshop, 1992-96 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Internship Resources, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Asian Americans for Community Involvement, 1992-93 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - San Jose Mayor Internships, Local Government Internship Program, 1991-95 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Peninsula Community Foundation, Local Government Internship Program, 1987-92 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Community Foundation of Santa Clara County, Local Government Internship Program, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - San Mateo County Fellowship Program, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Files
      - Watsonville Spring Break Trip, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Earthquake Relief, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Public Service Network, 1990-93 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - International Service
      - International Service, 1986-88, many undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - International Development Guide, 1986-9 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - International Fellowships, 1989, many undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - International Career Week, 1988-90 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Student Applications to Programs.
      - Local Government Internship Program Applications, circa 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Local Government Internship Program Applications, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Applications, 1987-88 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Applications, 1988-89 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Applications, 1989-90 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Applications, 1990-91 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Applications, 1991-92 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Applications, 1992-93 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Programs
      - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Program (includes photographs), 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Program (includes photographs), 1989-90 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Program (includes photographs), 1990-91 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Program (includes photographs), 1991-92 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Program, 1992-93 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Haas Center Programs and Courses
      - America Reads, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Community Impact, 1996-97 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Program Planning Group, 1995-97 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Dialogue Series, 1997-98 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Public Service Program for Community Leadership, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Schools Programs, 1997-98 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Visiting Mentor Tony Massengale, 1993-94 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Summer of Service Program, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Dreams of a City, Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - East Palo Alto Volunteer Booklet, May 1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Directory of Stanford Programs in EPA, Dec.1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - LINCS [Learning by Integrating Curriculum and Service]: Practicum on EPA, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Public Policy 182, 1987-93 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Public Policy 179, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Public Service Minor, Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Summer Institute on Service-Learning, 1994-96 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Empty the Shelters, 1992-93 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Advocacy, 1993; 1 undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Collaboration, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Interview transcripts, Public Service Center Video, Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - ESP [Educational Studies Program], 2002-06 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - You Can Make A Difference Conference 1984, 7/83-3/84 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - VIA [Volunteers in Asia], Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Community Service Film Proposal, ca. 1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Fellowship Proposal, March 1984 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Student Perspectives, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - 3 discs of digital files, each with descriptive list: Danielle Moore (PS Intern 2004-05); student group ESP compiled 2004; Jackie Schmidt-Posner assorted files 1995-99 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Chronicles, Subseries 4
    This subseries includes correspondence of Catherine Milton and Tim Stanton, as well as files relating to programs including fellowships, Stanford in Washington, You Can Make a Difference conferences, and schools programs.
    - Chronicles, 1983-May 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Chronicles, April-October 1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Chronicles, October-December 1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Chronicles, Dec. 1984-Sept.1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Chronicles, Oct.-Dec. 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Chronicles, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Chronicles, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Chronicles, Jan.-May 1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Chronicles, July-Dec. 1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Chronicles, 1990-91 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Chronicles, 1991-Jan. 1992 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Chronicles, Feb.-Aug. 1992 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Chronicles, Sept. 1992-July 1993 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Chronicles, October 1993-July 1994 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Fellowship Program, Subseries 5
    - Fellowships Program Materials, 4/84-10/84 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Fellowships Applications and Interview Notes, 5/84 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Fellowships Analysis, 8-12/84 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Fellowships Program Materials, 1/85-7/85 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Fellowships Analysis, 9/85 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Fellowships Program Materials, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fellowship Applications and Evaluations, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Fellowships Program Materials, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Fellowship Evaluations, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Fellowship Applications, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Fellowships Program Materials, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Fellowships Evaluations and Reports, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Fellowship Applications, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Fellowships Program Materials, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Fellowships Evaluations and Reports, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Fellowship Applications, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Fellowships Program Materials and Mid-Summer Reports, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Fellowships Evaluations, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Fellowship Applications, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Arts Fellowship Applications, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Fellowships Program Materials, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Fellowship Applications, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Fellowships Reports and Evaluations, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Fellowships Reports and Evaluations, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Fellowship Applications, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Fellowships Reports and Evaluations, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Fellowships Program Materials, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Strauss Scholarship 1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Fellowship Applications, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Fellowships Reports and Evaluations, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Fellowships Program Materials, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Fellowship Applications, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Fellowships Reports and Evaluations, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Biehl Fellowship 1998 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Fellowship Applications, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Fellowships Reports, Evaluations, and Letters, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Biehl Fellowship 1999 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Urban Summer Fellowship 2000 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Biehl Fellowship 2000 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Abrams Public Interest Law Fellowship 2000 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Sand Hill Philanthropy Fellowships 2000 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Haas Summer Fellowships 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Watsonville Earthquake Relief Photographs, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Open House Photographs, 9/04 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Fellowships Photographs, 2002 and undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Assorted Photographs, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Files from Jackie Schmidt-Posner (Interim Managing Direcor) and Suzanne Abel (Director of External Relations), Subseries 6
    - Beechwood School, 5/97-9/00 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Arts for Youth Fellowship, 11-12/02 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - National Advisory Board [NAB] 1998 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Earthquake Relief, 10-11/89 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - NAB 1999, 1-5/99 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Contacts, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Outreach, 1996-98 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Tutoring and Schools Programs Files, Subseries 7
    - EPASA/Manhattan Tutoring Project, 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Barrio Assistance, 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Brentwood Oaks Tutoring Project, 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Costano Tutoring, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Garden Oaks Tutoring, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Marva Collins Tutoring, 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Ravenswood Middle School Tutoring, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Stanford Tutoring Programs, 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Other School Programs, 1985 and undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Ravenswood-Stanford Tutoring Programs, 1987-88 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Tutoring Program Applications, 1987-88 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Tutoring Program Rosters, 1987-88 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Ravenswood-Stanford Tutoring Programs, 1988-89 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Parent Questionnaires, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Tutoring Objectives Worksheets, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Student Questionnaires, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Ravenswood-Stanford Tutoring Programs, 1989-90 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Tutoring Program Applications, 1989-90 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Bay Area Tutoring Conference, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Bay Area Tutoring Conference Registration Packet 3/89 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Haas Center Building Files, Subseries 8
    - Space Needs and Search, 1986-90 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Building Project, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Budget and Planning, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Building Plans and Blueprints, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Jeanne Halleck Files on Gardner Fellowship, Subseries 9
    - Gardner Fellowship Stewardship Letters, 1991-2005 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Gardner Fellowship Assorted Materials, 1989-2002 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Campus Compact Files, Subseries 10
    - Campus Compact 1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Campus Compact 1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Assorted Campus Compact Materials, 1988-92 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Campus Compact Executive Committee Meeting Materials, 1988-92 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Campus Compact 1992 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Academic Forum April 1990 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Upward Bound Files, Subseries 11
    - Upward Bound Scrapbook (photographs, relevant articles, names of students and programs, and other assorted materials), 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Upward Bound Slides, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Upward Bound Press Archives, 1991-1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Upward Bound Slides circa 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Upward Bound Slides circa 1992 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Upward Bound Slides circa 1994-2000 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Restricted Files, Subseries 12
    - AACI Applications (removed from box 3) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 1984 Fellowship applicant ratings (removed from box 7) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Teacher Questionnaires removed (from box 13) (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2012-033
  - Files from Damali Robertson (External Relations Coordinator), Subseries 1
    - Stanford Exchange for Public Service (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Senior Survey Comments, 1999 Jun (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Public Service Program for Community Leadership Applications, 1996 Feb (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Updates, Profiles, and Surveys, 1989-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Senior Profiles, 1991-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Young Alums in Public Service, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - ASB Leadership Applications, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Fellowships, 1997 and undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Roland Prize Nominees and Winners, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Donors Joseph Karger Memorial Fund, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Donors Benjamin Rome, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Donors 1988-1992 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Donors Boone Foundation, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Donors Rockefeller, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - List of Haas Classes and Programs, 1986-2002 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Stanford in Government, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - State and Local Evaluation, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Fellowship Supervisors Evaluation, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Files from Suzanne Abel (Director of External Relations), Subseries 2
    - Interview Transcripts for Haas Center Documentary, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network 1/3, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network 2/3, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network 3/3, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Gardner Orientation Manual, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Yearbook, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - SIG [Stanford in Government] 1/3, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - SIG [Stanford in Government] 2/3, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - SIG [Stanford in Government] 3/3, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - SIG International Fellowships, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Haas Political Curriculum, 2000 June (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - FSC [Faculty Steering Committee], 1999 Feb (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - FSC, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - NAB [National Advisory Board], 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Haas Center Vision and Mission, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Strategic Planning, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Service-Learning Institute, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - RCSD [Ravenswood City School District] Partnership, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Policy, Development, and Planning Coordination Committee 1/2, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Policy, Development, and Planning Coordination Committee 2/2, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - D.C. Campus, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Upward Bound Grant Proposal 1/3, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Upward Bound Grant Proposal 2/3, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Upward Bound Grant Proposal 3/3, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - EPANII [East Palo Alto Neighborhood Improvement Initiative] 1/3, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - EPANII [East Palo Alto Neighborhood Improvement Initiative] 2/3, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - EPANII [East Palo Alto Neighborhood Improvement Initiative] 3/3, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - EPANII, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Files from Jackie Schmidt-Posner (Interim Managing Director), Subseries 3
    - Public Service Scholars Program [PSSP] Portraiture Project, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Senior Survey, 1984, 1986-1990, 1996, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Long Range Planning, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Evaluation Committee, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Ravenswood Stanford Tutoring Program Manual, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Stanford in Washington Evaluations, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Visiting Mentor Program files, Subseries 4
    - Visiting Mentors Program, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Visiting Mentor Program, 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Tony Massengale (Visiting Mentor 1994) (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Tony Massengale (Visiting Mentor 1994), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Marti Leicester (Visiting Mentor 1995), 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - David Hilfiker (Visiting Mentor 1995), 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Suzan Shown Harjo (Visiting Mentor 1996) (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Linda Wong (Visiting Mentor 1996) (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Stuart Burden (Visiting Mentor 1996) (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Chris Avery (Visiting Mentor 1997) (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Lorne Needle (Visiting Mentor 1998) (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Paul Loeb (Visiting Mentor 1999) (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Sarah von der Lippe (Visiting Mentor 1999) (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Jim Pitofsky (Visiting Mentor 2000) (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Michael Huffington (Visiting Mentor 2001) (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Jose Padilla (Visiting Mentor 2001) (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Debora Norris (Visiting Mentor 2002) (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Darrell Armstrong (Visiting Mentor 2002) (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Sunne McPeak (Visiting Mentor 2003) (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Visiting Mentors Program, 1993-1999 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Visiting Mentors Program, 1994-2002 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Call to Serve Program Files, Subseries 5
    - Call to Serve program, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Recruiting Alumni - SAA, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - 2005-06 Programming, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Materials/Resources, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Partnership for Public Service, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Faculty, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Research, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Recruitment initiative, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Local government, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Public Service Career Network, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - 2005-06 Summary and Goals, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Committee and News, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Call to serve Initiative 1/4, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Call to serve Initiative 2/4, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Call to serve Initiative 3/4, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Call to serve Initiative 4/4, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Alpha Phi Omega FIles, Subseries 6
    - 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 1995-1999 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Year Unknown, circa 1990-2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Recent Fliers, 2000-2007 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Applications for pledge and membership, 1948-1958 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Records of 1958-64 pledge classes, 1958-1964 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Digital files and index of content, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Certificates, 1973-2002 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Students for Sustainability Files, Subseries 7
    - Conservation Cup, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Awareness Handouts/Stickers, 2005-2007 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Green Dorm, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Sustainability at Stanford, 2002-2007 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Posters, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "Grow" Program Files, Subseries 8
    - Fliers, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Compilation of Documents - Grow 1/2, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Compilation of Documents - Grow 2/2, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Audiovisual Materials, Subseries 9
    - Dis O 94 Open, 1994; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Worker Speak Out, 1999; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Bio 17, 1999 Jan 5; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Bio 17, 1999 Jan 12; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Bio 17, 1999 Jan 19 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Bio 17, 1999 Feb 2; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Bio 17, 1999 Feb 9; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Bio 17, 1999 Feb 16; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Bio 17, 1999 Mar 9; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Bio 17, 1999 Mar 22; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Sweating for a T-shirt, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Zoned for Slavery, 1995; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Seattle '99, 1999; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Bui Doi, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Youth Organizing, 1999; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Strawberries SEAS, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Infectious Waste Treatment, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Creative Empowerment, 1999; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Sierrans, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - The Rotten Truth, 3/2/1, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The energy Report, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - HECC- Energy Report, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Daw Aung Sun Sun Interview, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Test of time, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Garbage in America, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Partnerships, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Ancient Forests, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Madeline Muir, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Burma Diary, 1997; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Guatemala, 1990; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Stopping the coming ice age, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Environmental Vision, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Granting a future to green roots, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Ancient Futures, 1993; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Friends of Mount Graham, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Misconceptions Seminar, 1 optical disc(s) (cd-rom) (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Global Warming "The Heat is on", 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Environmental Justice + Racism, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Cookies and Tea w/students, 1997; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Prop 21 Discussion, 2000; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Monster R.E.M, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Energy policy, 1991; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Haverford, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Ecoconference #1, 1.0 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Ecoconference #2, 1.0 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Ecoconference #3, 1.0 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 12, Folder 16)